Solley mss., 1888-2006 LMC 2885
Lilly Library
- Miscellaneous
  - Aston – No. 1, 1999 (Box 23)
  - Aston – No. 2, 2000 (Box 23)
  - Aston – No. 5, 2003 (Box 23)
  - Aston – No. 6, 2004 (Box 23)
  - L'Auto-Carrosserie – No. 17, 1913 (Sept.) (Box 23)
  - Auto-Retro – No. 124, 1990 (Dec.) (Box 23)
  - The Autocar – Coronation Number, 1953 (May 8) (Box 23)
  - Automotive History Review – No. 30, 1996 (Summer) (Box 23)
  - Automotive History Review – No. 35, 1999-2000 (Winter) (Box 23)
  - Automotive History Review – No. 38, 2002 (Winter) (Box 23)
  - Automotive History Review – No. 39, 2002 (Fall) (Box 23)
  - Automotive History Review – No. 43, 2005 (Spring) (Box 23)
  - Automotive News – "Celebrating the 40th Anniversary – Packard", 1940 (Feb. 5) (Box 23)
  - The Bulb Horn – Vol. 7, no. 2, 1946 (Apr.) (Box 23)
  - La Carrosserie – "Salon 1927", 1927 (Oct.) (Box 23)
  - La Carrosserie – "Salon 1929" (Box 23)
  - La Cigogne – No. 4, 2001 (Sept.) (Box 23)
  - Du, 1987 (Oct.) (Box 23)
  - L'equipement Automobile – No. 117, 1927 (Mar.) (Box 23)
  - L'equipement Automobile – No. 157, 1930 (July) (Box 23)
  - L'equipement Automobile – No. 259, 1947 (Oct.) (Box 23)
  - L'equipement Automobile – No. 267, 1949 (Oct.) (Box 23)
  - Hispano–Suiza Society Newsletter – Nos. 64–76, 1991 (Dec.) – 1994 (Dec.) (Box 23)
  - Hispano–Suiza Society Newsletter – Nos. 77–90, 1995 (Mar.) – 1998 (June) (Box 23)
  - Hispano–Suiza Society Newsletter – Nos. 91–100, 1988 (Sept.) – 2000 (Nov.) (Box 23)
  - Hispano–Suiza Society Newsletter – Nos. 101–110, 2001 (Feb.) – 2003 (May) (Box 23)
  - Hispano–Suiza Society Newsletter – Nos. 112–122, 2003 (Aug.) – 2006 (Feb.) (Box 23)
  - Illustrierte Automobil Revue – Katalognummer 1950 (Box 23)
  - Illustrierte Automobil Revue – Katalognummer 1953 (Box 23)
  - Illustrierte Automobil Revue – Katalognummer 1954 (Box 23)
  - Leonard – "Hommage an Leonardo Da Vinci...Daimlerchrsyler", 2000 (Box 23)
  - Life – "100 Years of the Automobile in America", 1996 (Winter) (Box 23)
  - La Manovella – Vol. 40, no. 7, 2000 (Sept.) (Box 23)
  - The Motor – Vol. 90, no. 2340, 1946 (Oct. 30) (Box 23)
  - The Motor – "The London Motor Show", 1952 (Oct. 22) (Box 23)
  - The Motor – No. 2659, 1953 (Jan. 28) (Box 23)
  - The Motor – "The London Motor Show", 1953 (Oct. 21) (Box 23)
  - The Motor – Vol. 113, no. 2926, 1958 (Apr. 23) (Box 23)
  - Motor Sport – Vol. 63, no. 8, 1987 (Aug.) (Box 23)
  - SAH Journal – No. 201, 2002 (Nov.–Dec.) (Box 23)
  - The Way of the Zephyr – Vol. 36, no. 3, 2003 (May–June) (Box 23)